Have DQ checks and balance reconciliation
checks for this particular config table,
right?
That is the reason why we can directly
instead of.
So here, let me share my screen with it.
So here batch task flow will be and we'll
having extra group level task flow also,
right.
So in the group level task flow where we
have this job preload this this job level
task flow, right that I'm explaining here.
So here instead of this job ABC job
preload,
we'll have only one component that is job
preload.
Yeah.
Because the rest of them are not actually
not.
Yeah, yeah.
And it is also a truncate and reload rate.
That is the reason why we don't have even
this source window function.
And also we don't have like you checks.
So we don't have the load to job role
execution log.
And also, yeah, that's it.
And also restart.
OK, this clean up,
skipping the stage load,
all these are not not required because we
don't have any stage tables.
Yeah, event, right.
OK,
So we can directly use this particular
task flow, OK.
And in case of this failure,
we have to send out a notification, OK.
And then we can use this testing task.
So it is basically in case of restart,
if my particular job load is already
completed, we have to skip that job,
right?
So we have to add this testing task OK.
After that here we can directly have our
job.
So this will be simply like this instead
of sub task flow,
we'll have a mapping task OK,
data task which will load the data into
right which will make an entry into my
job runstart spread out table.
If if it fails,
we can just add a notification task under
throw step to file the task flow.
And we'll add a notification task to
notify that this has failed like this
particular job load has failed at this
point like that.
After that, we'll have a skip task flow.
Sorry, skip decision task where if,
if it is why?
We'll just skip and we'll go to that.
Else it will load a loader map.
So whatever this this will hold a fully
parameterized 1 to one mapping.
Yeah, OK.
If it is failed,
there is 11 component one mapping task.
Let me open this quickly.
Job run starts post load failure,
is there right?
So we can just use this part instead of
this Yes, of the entire task, right?
Yeah.
Once this is completed,
we're here in the job post load success,
we don't have even arena are it right?
So we can we can just directly use this
Job run starts preload mapping task and
notification task and this session has
failed.
Your failure step also not is required.
If this execution gets failed,
We just need to use this use this part
directly, right?
Who makes sense?
And so Ishwara, these components, right?
So the components will remain the same
like when I see the components,
the mapping task, right?
So I'll like we can just replicate those
mapping tasks like copy those mapping
tasks from the broker one which is the
latest and up into our RTMI configuration
CBC folder.
Yeah, yeah, you can copy that and that OK,
it's OK.
I'll just even for conference.
Yes, yes, I'll just update that.
I'll let you know in case any questions.
OK.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Thank you.
Thank you team.
If thank you.
Thank you team.